<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
   	 
   	<string name="russian_dialogcontent">Чтобы уменьшить размер установочного файла, в новой версии мы удалили поддержку интерфейсом русского языка.
Для использования русского языка установите языковой пакет.
Нажмите на кнопку, чтобы загрузить языковой пакет.</string>
   	<string name="russian_notification">Языковой пакет Go Launcher
Используйте Go Launcher с русским языком.</string>
   	
   	<string name="hebrew_dialogcontent">לתשומת לבכם
כדי להפחית את הגודל של קובץ ההתקנה, הסרנו את הקובץ של השפה העברית בגירסה החדשה.
הינכם עדיין יכולים להשתמש ב-Go Launcher בעברית ע”י שימוש בחבילת השפה.
לחץ על כפתור ההורדה כדי לקבל את חבילת השפה.
</string>
   	<string name="hebrew_notification">חבילת השפה של Go Launcher
השתמש ב-Go Launcher בעברית
</string>
   	
   	<string name="romanian_dialogcontent">Atentie
Pentru a reduce dimensiunea pachetului de instalare am eliminat resursa pentru limba Română din noua versiune.
Puteti totusi folosi Go Launcher în limba Română prin folosirea pachetului de limbă.
Click pe butonul de descărcare pentru a obtine pachetul de limbă.
</string>
   	<string name="romanian_notification">GO Launcher Pachet Limbă
Folositi GO Launcher în Limba Română
</string>

   	<string name="spanish_dialogcontent">Atención
Para reducir el tamaño del archivo de instalación, hemos eliminado los recursos del idioma español en la nueva versión.
Aún puedes usar GO Launcher en español utilizando el pack de idioma.
Pulsa el botón descargar para obtener el pack de idioma.
</string>
   	<string name="spanish_notification">Pack de Idioma de GO Launcher
Uso de GO Launcher en Español.
</string>	
   	
   	<string name="italiano_dialogcontent">Attenzione
Per ridurre la dimensione del file di installazione, abbiamo rimosso dalla nuova versione la risorsa della lingua italiana.
Potrai utilizzare ancora GO Launcher in Italiano, scaricando il relativo language pack.
Clicca il bottone di download per ottenere il language pack.
</string>
   	<string name="italiano_notification">GO Launcher Language Pack
Utilizza GO Launcher in Italiano.
</string>
   	
   	<string name="german_dialogcontent">Achtung
Um die Größe der Installationsdatei zu reduzieren, haben wir in der neuen Version die Sprache Deutsch entfernt.
Um GO Launchen weiterhin in Deutsch zu benutzen muss das Sprachpaket benutzt werden.
Klicken Sie auf den Download Button um das Sprachpaket zu bekommen.
</string>
   	<string name="german_notification">GO Launcher Sprachpaket
GO Launcher in deutsch benutzen
</string>
   	
   	<string name="turkish_dialogcontent">Dikkat
Yükleme dosyasının boyutunu küçültmek için, yeni versiyonda Türkçe dil paketini kaldırdık.
Buna rağmen GO Launcher’i Türkçe dil paketini indirerek kendi dilinizde kullanabilirsiniz.
İndirme butoununa tıklayarak dil paketini indirebilirsiniz.
</string>
   	<string name="turkish_notification">GO Launcher Dil Paketi
GO Launcher’i Türkçe olarak kullan.
</string>

   	<string name="polish_dialogcontent">Aby zmniejszyć rozmiar pliku instalacyjnego, usunęliśmy z nowej wersji polskie tłumaczenie.
Można nadal korzystać z GO Launcher w języku polskim za pomocą pakietu językowego.
Kliknij przycisk Pobierz, aby pobrać polski pakiet językowy.
</string>
   	<string name="polish_notification">Tłumaczenie do GO Launcher
Korzystaj z Go Launchera w języku polskim.
</string>	
   	
   	<string name="portugu_dialogcontent">Atenção
Para reduzir o tamanho do arquivo de instalação, nós removemos o pacote de idioma Português Brasil na nova versão.
Você ainda pode usar o GO Launcher em Português Brasil usando o pacote de idioma.
Clique no botão download para obter o pacote de idioma.
</string>
   	<string name="portugu_notification">Pacote de Idioma do GO Launcher
Use GO Launcher em Português Brasil.
</string>
   	
   	<string name="french_dialogcontent">Attention
Pour réduire la taille du fichier d’installation, nous retirons le language français dans la nouvelle version.
Vous pouvez toujours utiliser GO Launcher en français en utilisant le pack linguistique.
Cliquez sur le bouton de téléchargement pour récupérer le pack de linguistique.
</string>
   	<string name="french_notification">Pack Linguistique GO Launcher
Utilisez GO Launcher en français.
</string>
   	
   	<string name="japanese_dialogcontent">注意
インストール後のファイルサイズを減らす為、我々は最新バージョンで”日本語”の言語リソースを削除しました。
GO Launcherを”日本語”で使用するには言語パックを導入して下さい。
ダウンロードボタンをクリックする事で言語パックを入手できます。
</string>
   	<string name="japanese_notification">GO Launcher 言語パック
GO Launcherを”日本語”で使用する
</string>

   	<string name="vietnamese_dialogcontent">Chú ý
để giảm kích thước gói cài đặt, chúng tôi đã xóa gói ngôn ngữ xx trong phiên bản mới
Bạn vẫn có thể sử dụng ngôn ngữ Việt trong Go Launcher bằng cách sử dụng gói ngôn ngữ
Bấm vào nút Download để tải nó
</string>
   	<string name="vietnamese_notification">Gói ngôn ngữ Go Launcher
Sử dụng ngôn ngữ Việt trong Go Launcher
</string>	
   	
   	<string name="indonesia_dialogcontent">Perhatian
Untuk mengurangi ukuran berkas instalasi, kami telah menghapus bahasa xx dalam versi yang baru.
Anda tetap bisa menggunakan Go Launcher dalam bahasa Indonesia dengan menggunakan paket bahasa.
</string>
   	<string name="indonesia_notification">Ketuk tombol download untuk mendapatkan paket bahasa.
Gunakan GO Launcher dalam bahasa Indonesia.
</string>
   	
   	<string name="swedish_dialogcontent">Observera
För att minska installationsfilens storlek har vi tagit bort språkpaketet svenska i den nya versionen.
Du kan fortfarande använda GO Launcher på svenska genom att installera språkpaketet.
Klicka på nedladdningsknappen för att ladda ner språkpaketet.
</string>
   	<string name="swedish_notification">GO Launcher språkpaket
Använd GO Launcher på svenska.
</string>
   	
   	<string name="persian_dialogcontent">توجه
برای کاهش اندازه فایل نصبی, ما منبع زبانی فارسی را در نسخه جدید پاک خواهیم کرد.
شما همچنان قادر به استفاده از GO Launcher به زبان فارسی با استفاده از بسته های زبانی خواهید بود.
برای دریافت بسته زبانی بر روی دکمه دانلود کلیک کنید.
</string>
   	<string name="persian_notification">بسته زبانی GO Launcher
استفاده از GO Launcher به زبان فارسی.
</string>

   	<string name="croatian_dialogcontent">Pozor
U cilju smanjenja veličine instalacijske datoteke, u novoj verziji uklonili smo hrvatski jezik.
I dalje možete koristiti Go Launcher na hrvatskom jeziku pomoću jezičnog paketa.
Kliknite na gumb Preuzmi (Download) da biste preuzeli jezični paket.
</string>
   	<string name="croatian_notification">Jezični paket za Go Launcher
Koristite Go Launcher na hrvatskom jeziku.
</string>	
   	
   	<string name="serbian_dialogcontent">Upozorenje
Kako bismo smanjili veličinu datoteke za instalaciju, u novoj verziji uklonili smo jezički paket za srpski/crnogorski/bosanski jezik.
I dalje možete koristiti Go Launcher na srpskom/crnogorskom/bosanskom jeziku tako što ćete preuzeti jezički paket.
Kliknite na dugme Preuzmi (Download) kako biste preuzeli jezički paket.
</string>
   	<string name="serbian_notification">Jezički paket za Go Launcher
Koristite Go Launcher na srpskom/crnogorskom/bosanskom jeziku
</string>
   	
   	<string name="hongkong_dialogcontent">為了減小GO桌面的安裝包大小，我們在這個版本將刪除繁體中文的語言資源。
但您仍可以通過下載語言包來使用繁體中文。
請點擊下方的下載按鈕進行下載。</string>
   	<string name="hongkong_notification">GO桌面語言包
使用繁體中文的GO桌面</string>
</resources>
